<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" ?>
<termsofservice>
	<section>
		<sectionhead>Acceptance</sectionhead>
		<sectionbody>By accessing and browsing this website or by using and/or downloading any content from same, you agree and accept the Terms of Use as set forth below.</sectionbody>
	</section>
	<section>
		<sectionhead>Links to 3rd-Party Websites</sectionhead>
		<sectionbody>Links to third-party web sites are provided for convenience only and do not imply any approval or endorsement by dotNetBB.com of the linked sites, as such sites are beyond our control. Thus, dotNetBB.com cannot be held responsible for the content of any linked site or any link contained therein.</sectionbody>
	</section>
	<section>
		<sectionhead>Intellectual Property</sectionhead>
		<sectionbody>
			This message board is protected by intellectual property rights and is the exclusive property of &lt;a href=mailto:Andrew@dotNetBB.com&gt;Andrew Putnam&lt;/a&gt;. Any material that it contains, including, but not limited to, texts, data, graphics, pictures, sounds, videos, logos, icons or HTML code is protected under intellectual property law and remains Andrew Putnam's or third party's property.
			&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You may use this material for personal and non-commercial purposes in accordance with the principles governing intellectual property law. Any other use or modification of the content of dotNetBB.com web site without the Clan's prior written authorization is prohibited.
		</sectionbody>
	</section>
	<section>
		<sectionhead>Privacy</sectionhead>
		<sectionbody>
			dotNetBB.com collects minimal statistical information from the users of the website. Our statistical reporting system records our server requests. This system stores the users IP, date, and nature of access. dotNetBB.com does not sell any user information stored on the system. dotNetBB.com does not give out any user information to any 3rd party companies.
			&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This site may use "cookies" to track users traffic patterns. A cookie is an element of data that a web site can send to your browser, which may then store it on your system. These cookies are used to assist you in reaching the appropriate information and make your visit tailored to your individual preferences. You are free to decline these cookies by setting your browser accordingly; however, refusing the cookies may prevent you from accessing some pages of the web site.
		</sectionbody>
	</section>
	<section>
		<sectionhead>Questions</sectionhead>
		<sectionbody>Should you have any other question or request regarding our terms of use, please contact &lt;a href=mailto:Andrew@dotNetBB.com&gt;Andrew@dotNetBB.com&lt;/a&gt;.</sectionbody>
	</section>
	
</termsofservice>	

